<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Random Itch</title>
    <link>https://niklas-olsson.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Random Itch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://niklas-olsson.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Categories vs. Tags - Organizing Your Digital Waypoints</title>
      <link>https://niklas-olsson.github.io/insights/categories-vs-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://niklas-olsson.github.io/insights/categories-vs-tags/</guid>
      <description>When curating a collection of resources, such as the &amp;ldquo;Waypoints&amp;rdquo; on this site, a common question arises: how best to organize them? Two primary methods often come to mind: categories and tags.&#xA;While seemingly similar, they serve distinct purposes and offer different levels of granularity for content organization and discoverability.&#xA;Categories: Broad Buckets for Primary Classification Categories are best thought of as broad, mutually exclusive groups. Each item typically belongs to one, and only one, category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Conductor</title>
      <link>https://niklas-olsson.github.io/projects/the-conductor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://niklas-olsson.github.io/projects/the-conductor/</guid>
      <description>Technology Stack Operational Flow States and Phases Summary This state machine model for &amp;ldquo;The Conductor&amp;rdquo; is conceptually sound and highly workable for an autonomous, self-optimizing system. It effectively captures the essence of a continuous improvement loop.&#xA;Workability and Achievement: This model is highly workable for an automated system because each state&amp;rsquo;s criteria and each transition&amp;rsquo;s trigger are defined in objective, verifiable, and automatable terms. There are no ambiguous &amp;ldquo;approvals&amp;rdquo; or subjective human judgments required for progression.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
